Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development UP191
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development
1986 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Center for the Study of Drug Development
UP191
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the newsletter for the Center for the Study of Drug Development. It highlights events at the Center and in the field of drug development. It became the Tufts CSDD Newsletter, published 3 times a year by the Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development.
- Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1986 -- 2014; 1986 -- 1991; UP191.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the newsletter for the Center for the Study of Drug Development. It highlights events at the Center and in the field of drug development. It became the Tufts CSDD Newsletter, published 3 times a year by the Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1986; UP191.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    January, June (2), and October issues.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1987; UP191.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    March (2), May (2), and September (2) issues.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1988; UP191.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    February (2), and September issues.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1989; UP191.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    May and September issues.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1990; UP191.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    February issue.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1991; UP191.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1996; UP191.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    October issue.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1997; UP191.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    March and September issues.
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1998; UP191.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Newsletter of the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 2014; UP191.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    September/October
    Volume, issue
    16, 5